

SEMYON MOROZOV

Backend Developer



Address Krasnodar, Russia



Phone +7 969 305 55 07



<u>**Telegram**</u> t.me/justSeme



Mail

semyn03@mail.ru



Github

https://github.com/JustSeme



<u>LinkedIn</u>

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ семён-морозов-261b45255/



<u>CodeWars</u>

https://www.codewars.com/users/JustSemen

ABOUT ME

Good afternoon, I am an experienced developer with 1.5+ experience in creating
Fullstack applications based on technology:
Backend: Typescript, Nest.is, postgreSQL, typeORM, express, mongoDB, mongoose

Frontend: React, Redux, React-hooks, React class-components, axios, adaptive layout

Now I'm going deeper into the backend direction and expanding my technical horizon into creating applications based on the node-telegram-bot-api.

In my free time I like to read IT literature (now I'm reading "Grok Algorithms" by Aditya Bhargava) and solve puzzles on codeWars.

I am open to your suggestions!

EDUCATION

IT-INCUBATOR

Technology stack:
TypeScript, Node.js,
Nest.js/express,
PostgreSQL/MongoDB
TypeORM/mongoose

01.01.2023 - 30.07.2023

МКИБД

Programming in computer systems 2018-2022

HTML-Academy

Technology stack: HTML, CSS, SASS, JavaScript

2019 - 2020

SKILLS

- JavaScript, TypeScript, SQL
- Node.JS, Nest.JS, Express.JS
- PostgreSQL, MongoDB
- TypeORM, mongoose
- TDD, e2e tests, jest, supertest
- REST API, axios
- React.js, React-hooks, Redux
- HTML, CSS, SASS, Grid, Flexbox
- Git, Swagger, Postman

LANGUAGES

RUSSIAN - Native

ENGLISH - Pre-Intermediate (B1)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Gopolos Studios

Fullstack Developer

June 2022 - May 2023

Development of client and server (mostly) parts of web applications in a team. I used the following technologies in my projects:

- TypeScript, SQL, Node.js, Nest.js, Express, postgreSQL, MongoDB, React, Redux, axios, jest, supertest

Functionality:

- CRUD transactions protected by Bearer authorization with JWT
- Registration, login, logout operations for users using Bcrypt
- Validation of incoming requests with class-validator
- Pagination, search and sorting for GET requests Sending emails from nodemailer
- Saving and managing active user sessions (the user can manage sessions personally)

<u>Client</u> - https://github.com/JustSeme/ReactWayOfSamurai <u>Server</u> - https://github.com/JustSeme/blogPlatform-NestJS

Rubicon Digital AgencyFrontend Developer

December 2021 - April 2022
Development of widgets for the amoCRM platform in
conjunction with the REST API backender, using native (+jQuery)
tools, design development, web interface, forms, adaptive and
flexible layout, processing, displaying a large amount of data,
working with the server via http requests (ajax)

Total development experience - 1.5 years

Website